[{"answer": "Weak, scary.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 14, "question": "What is your view of George Zimmerman?", "qSentId": 13}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 20, "question": "Do you feel that your testimony strongly impacted the case at all?", "qSentId": 19}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "In a negative way?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "You're very famous now.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Hi, how are you?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "He was trying to get home, and he was, and that's a fact.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "In your heart, what do you believe happened?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "And you know that because you were talking to him?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "All day.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "How often would you talk to Trayvon?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Yes, all day.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "All day long?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "He was a calm, chill, loving person.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "What kind of guy was he?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Really, what we were going to be in life.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "What would you talk about?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "He was a good friend to you?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "A kind friend?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "Was he ever aggressive?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Did you ever see him aggressive?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Did he ever lose his temper?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "You mean the stuff on social media?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Did he ever talk to you about guns?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Did you ever see him with a gun?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Drugs.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "What about drugs?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "Did he take a lot of weed?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Like twice a week.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "How much would you say?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "Twice a week?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Is that normal for teenagers in your community?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "No, because I --", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "You would do the same?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Do you think they understood the world that you and Trayvon come from?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Don West.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Don West gave you a very hard time, the defense attorney?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "I'm going to have to say, he -- like I'm a Christian.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "What is your view of him?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "No, a bone.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "Which is a dental condition for your teeth?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Yes, I had to have surgery to push it back, and right now I don't want to do it, because it will take a year to heal.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "ORGAN: You had to have surgery for it?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Look at me, no.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Have you been bullied for that before?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "It's not that I didn't want to be there, it's a lot of stress.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Is that how you felt?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "And you were grieving a friend.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "I was dealing with a lot of stress for 16 months, I think?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Shock.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Particularly the shocking fact that you were the last person he was talking to?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "Do you miss him?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "Angry.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "What do you feel about what that juror said about you?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "I'm holding back.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "What did that make you feel just seeing him?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "Well, the juries, they see their fact.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "What's your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Cracka.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "How do you spell it, first of all?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "EANTEL: Yes, and that's a person who act like they are police, who like security guard, who acting like, that's what I said to them.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "C-R-A-C-K-A?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "No, I'm just trying to get home.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "And if George Zimmerman had done that, if he'd introduced himself as a neighborhood watch patrolman, even though he was off duty, if he'd done that, what would Trayvon have said to him, do you think?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "That was all he wanted to do?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "I'm finally going to get one, that night.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "When you heard the tape of George Zimmerman saying that these A-holes, these F-ing punks they're always getting away with it, before he has the confrontation with Trayvon, what did you think was going through George Zimmerman's mind when he said that?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "It was racial.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "And be honest with me, Rachel, do you think that that was racially motivated or more a case of somebody he thought was a young thug, black or white?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "No, not that.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Do you think it was just wrong that you had no black people on the jury at all?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "Whoop ass.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "Would Trayvon, if he had been attacked or had been confronted, and he was scared, would he have whooped ass, as you put it?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Yes, in my mind -- well, in reality, Trayvon, before his death, he thought I was still on the phone.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Would he have defended himself if he'd been in that position?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "But you -- but you felt that there was no doubt in your mind from what Trayvon was telling you on the phone about the creepy ass cracka and so on, that he absolutely believed that George Zimmerman, this man, you didn't know who he was at the time, but this man, was pursuing him?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "And he was freaked out by it?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Look at the picture.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "What was your reaction when you realized what she'd done?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Do you feel that your testimony strongly impacted the case at all?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "In a negative way?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Yes, well, now I'd be lying by saying that.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "Are you an honest person by nature?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "-- in a serious trial?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "Weak, scary, hiding from his father.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Well, what is your view of George Zimmerman?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "If you were a real man, you would have stand on that stage and tell what happened.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Why do you say that?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Yes, I understand what Don's trying to say, oh, I switched it around.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "Give evidence, you mean?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "Nigga.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "So was there anything you wished you have said when you were in there?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "People -- the whole world say it's a racist word.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "That means a male.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "What does that word mean to you?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "No, any kind of male.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "A black male?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Any kind -- Chinese could say nigga.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Black or white?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "They all say it.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "And that's what they mean?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Because that's the racist word.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "No, in a generation --", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "And they have just different meanings in -- in your community?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "Not young people.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "To young people, you mean?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Did Trayvon have that in him?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "I believe she did.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Do you think that she got an unfairly hard time in terms of the reaction to the evidence that she gave?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "I -- I couldn't hear your question --", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "What did you make of it, Cheney?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Yes, I -- I saw a part of it.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Did -- did you hear the interview I did with Rachel Jeantel, Trayvon Martin's friend just then?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I think that -- that she clearly had -- could have done a better job testifying if she had been properly prepared by the lawyers, given an opportunity to.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "I mean, do you think that justice has been done here?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Normal SOP.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "What -- what do you make of that?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "What -- what I know, Piers, is we don't know what somebody else thinks.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "And as Rachel suggested, how much was the jury's decision affected by the fact that they were effectively an all-white jury?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "Yes, I think it could have made a difference.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "If she'd be more like that Rachel on the stand, could it have made a difference?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "The law is the problem because the aggressor can then claim self-defense if the situation changes.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "Is it the law that's the problem?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "Jayne Weintraub, are we going to have a change to -- although \"Stand Your Ground\" wasn't used in this case, it is prevalent in many states in America.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "Do you think Florida or any other states will be making changes or modifications to the current \"Stand Your Ground\" law?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "Our Constitution guarantees the defendant a jury of his peers -- not a victim, a jury of his peers.", "docId": "130719pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "Jayne?", "qSentId": 660}]